David Frommont

29 Milner Road, Brighton BN2 4BS

07387 576977 - davidfrommont@gmail.com - GitHub: dfrommont

Personal Profile:

I am a methodical, organised 2nd year student at the University of Sussex who is taking Computer Science. I have a range of work experience across multiple fields, ranging from a timber trade group to an IT outsourcing company. My ability to handle tasks in a scientific manner, as shown by the chosen subject of study, is something I am proud of.

During my first year at university I joined HackSussex, a Computer Science society, and later it's committee. Here I was able to take part in a 24-hour Hackathon, run a livestream coding competition from the campus Tv studio and work on the new society website. HackSussex has allowed me to work on my confidence and Programming skills.

Work Experience:

Iceland Food Store Farnborough

April 2023 - September 2023: Sales Assistant

- Over the summer between my 1st and 2nd years of University I was trained to work in the store and on the tills.
- In this time I learnt new skills such as how to stock rotate correctly, operate a till, handle a range of customers and prevent stock loss

Price & Pierce Forest Products Griffin House, West Street, Woking, GU21 6BS

May 2020 - September 2020: Office Admin

• In this role, I placed orders for Stock and Sales and helped transfer between IT systems, as well as being in contact with customers and worked well as a part of the team. My time here allowed me to develop my team working and communication skills.

Xiria Ltd. Unit 2a Stanhope Gate, Stanhope Road, Camberley, Surrey, GU15 3DW

August 2019: Position IT Trainee

- In this role, I got to work with professionals from the IT industry working in an office and on site, including working within Gatwick Airport. This position originally started as a work experience placement but I was invited back to join the company again.
- My time with the company helped to show me what I wanted from my career and improved my IT skills.

Education:

September 2020 – 2022:

The Sixth Form College Farnborough, Prospect Avenue, Farnborough, Hants, GU14 8JX

June 2022:Computer ScienceA-levelA*PhysicsA-levelAMathsA-levelAExtended ProjectA-levelA

September 2015 - June 2020:

Tomlinscote School, Tomlinscote Way, Frimley, Camberley, Surrey, GU16 8PY

June 2020: 12 GCSEs including a 9 and 8 7's

Skills Profile:

- I pride myself on my organisation and communication skills, both in how I present myself and my work, being capable of both working alone and in a team.
- Having studied STEM subjects, I am confident with a range of IT softwares and as well as having great numeracy skills - I also work well to deadlines as demonstrated by my Extended Project Qualification.

Extra Curricular / Hobbies:

- I continue to play the violin, having achieved grades 1 through 3.
- I also enjoy reading, being a big fan of the fantasy genre.
- During my freetime, I code a lot, to build on skills I already know as well as playing video games on my PC.

Referee:

Dawn Arnold
The Sixth Form College Farnborough
Prospects Avenue
GU14 8JX
01252 688300
darnold@farnborough.ac.uk

Marie Tamasauskas
Price & Pierce
Griffin House, West Street
Woking, Surrey
GU21 6BS
01483 221800